hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Krakowski and this podcast is
where we help coaches trainers and
mentors grow in their business make more
money online giving you the strategies
tips and tricks that you need to create
the business that you want now we're in
episode number
215. we've been doing this podcast now
since though I think we started back in
um and you can go back and listen
through the episodes this podcast again
isn't intended to be listened through
sequentially each episode is its own
lesson now today I want to talk about
Facebook ads and what's working with
Facebook ads and how we're using chat
GPT to help us with our advertising
campaigns okay so I've done a number of
presentations a number of Zoom calls a
number of trainings on how to do this
but I wanted to just kind of break it
down for you in a succinct
uh just the meat and potatoes way with
this podcast episode if you only got you
know 20 30 minutes and you want to get
up to speed on what's working right now
that's what this is going to help you
with so
if you have not been a part of some of
the live events that we have been doing
we do live events every single month
uh and what are Live Events well like we
just did one on Saturday growing your
group coaching business with paid
advertising incredible experience highly
recommend next time we do something like
this for you to join us
um as well we're doing a five-day event
here coming up this week May 8th through
the 12th and so if you haven't
registered yet for that make sure to
join that if it's past the time of one
of these five-day events one of these
live events that we're doing this is the
best way to interact with us Beyond this
podcast because it is more interactive
and it gives you a chance to actually
ask questions and get your unique
problems solved beyond that we have our
coaching programs our group coaching
program the client growth accelerator
make sure that you get on the waiting
list for that that's the premiere top
coaching program uh specifically for
mentors speakers and coaches that want
to make six and seven figures online and
so you can join the waiting list to that
now if you haven't yet be sure to go
grab my chat GPT prompt download this
this download is over at my website and
I have it at the top of my site here
just because it's so valuable to people
so valuable for you to grab onto
is it's a Google doc and when you go
just put in your name and email address
over on my website it's going to give
you access to a Google doc that I call
it a living document because I'm
constantly updating the same document
it's my working document that I use in
my business
um to keep track of all the prompts that
we're using with chat GPT that's working
the best for us and so it's 36 pages
long
um and we use this for all of our sales
copywriting for all of our sales letters
and for all of our Facebook advertising
is we're using chat GPT and we're using
these artificial intelligence engines
now that are out there to be able to
write all of our sales copy we have a
methodology that injects the right
emotion into it and connects with
exactly what's going to convert well to
a client
one of the number one things that people
are missing when they create a sales
letter when they run Facebook ads as
they're not communicating the results or
outcome clearly and the ability to
communicate outcomes and results
for your potential client
okay in the macro we as people don't
want to become too attached to outcomes
things like that we want and I teach
about that learning to let go of our
attachment to how we envision things but
when you're selling something you want
to sell with a direct attachment to the
outcome that you're promising somebody
you and so the biggest mistake that I
see most coaches mentors and trainers
make is they beat around the bush around
what the outcome and the potential
outcome is that people have or want
and so this series of prompts right here
and if you're if you're listening to
this
um the video version on YouTube I'd
highly recommend checking out the video
version because you can actually see it
on the screen this series of prompts
right here step one says what is the
ultimate outcome of somebody who works
with the coach and these are prompts
that we're actually going to give to
chat CPT
based off of
whatever sales letter that we create so
a lot of people ask me Jeremiah how do
you target your Facebook ads the right
way well Facebook has changed everything
now in the last couple of years with iOS
14 when they went to Congress when
um
the just all the changes with artificial
intelligence has changed how they target
your ads and so now you used to get
really really specific with your
targeting and we would do a lot of
research to do that now the best way to
do it is you go really Broad
but you get real specific with your ad
copy and with your language with the
exact words to the the type of person
that you want to help
and the outcome they can experience okay
and so this is why I tell all coaches
all trainers all mentors all roads start
with your offer copy
don't even worry about figuring out the
technology figuring out how to read
reports how to make everything work
perfectly all of that until you have
your offer copy dialed in and now with
tools like chat GPT
and there's other tools out there you
know we're taking a look at there's one
um we're starting to play around with in
our group called open Assistant from
hugging face open assistant is a
completely open source version of what
chat CPT is
and it gives you access
to
um so chat gbt is like a commercial you
got to pay for it
open assistant is completely open source
which is super cool so AI is just
changing the landscape
of how
we communicate our products how we
communicate the value that we bring to
our customers and what it is is there is
a lot of like
thinking that was involved that you had
to intuitively understand
I fully believe that you need to bring
intuition into every single part of your
marketing every single part of your your
sales process
but when you can use a tool like chat
GPT or open Assistant I would recommend
still using gpt4 for right now
when you can use a tool like that to
help you come up with ideas
for your business
very specifically
it it
unlocks you to where
previously you used to have to take
spend a lot of time
getting to about
80 percent of the way to the finish line
now the AI helps you get here so with AI
assistant we're able to get to about
eighty percent of the finish line and
then use our intuition to get us to a
hundred back in the day we used to have
to basically use our intuition to get us
all the way to 100 from from 20 to 100
okay and that's how clearly we express
what we do with the client if you are a
a coach if you're a mentor if you're a
speaker if you're a trainer what is the
problem that you solve for a client
what pain points do they have what
struggles do they have what desires do
they have and what is the end result
outcome
and so if we go into chat GPT and let's
just take any topic right here let's
just say that you do a
online
uh yoga and
Fitness coaching okay
I always start with asking chat jpt
create me a sales letter for online Yoga
and Fitness coaching to promote a free
uh four-week class
transform your life with our four week
online yoga Fitness and coaching class
now here's the thing is you don't want
to and this is very important that I
stress this you don't want to
just use the language that chat GPT
gives you
right out of the box it's not going to
work well for you
if you treat it as law
as this is the final language I need to
use it's just that's not smart to do at
all because you're it's not it lacks the
human touch you need to bring your A lot
of the humanity into it and we have
these prompts help us bring that
Humanity into it and when you don't have
the the result or outcome clearly
expressed you're missing ninety percent
of that process so we have a couple of
props right here to list out the pain
points and all that and so we'll just go
through here and we will
enter some of this in and every time you
might be saying you know what does any
of this have to do with Facebook ads it
has everything to do with Facebook ads
it has everything to do with Facebook
ads because you're targeting in your
Facebook ad
and your ability to close the right
sales with the right Prospect have to do
with the words that you put on the page
the algorithm now with the ads manager
reads the actual words that are on your
landing page they're actually taking
the text that's on your page
this written text
and the text that's written in your ad
and the words that you're saying on your
video ads and deciding who to show your
ad to based on those words now
okay
and so when we understand that your
targeting has to do with getting these
words right
and most coaches trainers and mentors
they know what they do
they do a very poor job of expressing
what the end result outcome is and
connecting emotionally
to what actually triggers people to take
action with them okay so your job is you
want to
from your ad trigger somebody to take
action with you and be able to identify
that you understand what their pain is
what their struggle is and what their
ultimate outcome that they want is so
what we'll do is we'll go through and
we'll we'll have chat GPT I call it
processing
some of these answers right here what's
going to give us some of the pain points
but that's just going to get us a little
bit of the way to the finish line
the results and outcome generator is
what takes things to the next level
there's also the Epiphany Bridge prompt
if you haven't ran it through an
epiphany Bridge prompt I will go through
and do this as well usually okay let's
all type this in identify the main
problem solved the solution and outcome
and so this is going to actually help us
get to about 40 percent of the way there
then we'll use the results generator to
get about 70 percent and then we'll
re-craft that into what I call a
storytelling
um empathy based sales letter and then
we restructure that into a Facebook ad
and that becomes the best Facebook ads
for us so this process is what we're
doing is we're taking the idea of what
we do
as a coach as a mentor
online yoga Fitness coaching whatever
your thing is that you do
I always have it start with making just
a bracelet Baseline basic sales letter
and then I have it start to answer these
questions what are the pain points
have it run through the Epiphany Bridge
it creates a like sort of a fake
backstory of what somebody experiences
and then we go through and we use the
outcome results generator to create a
fictional narrative
as a two-step process you do step one
and then you do step two to dive deeper
and then we reverse engineer that back
into
our sales letter so
the idea is you want a clear picture
and in sales and marketing the ability
to demonstrate to people a clear picture
of the outcome that they will experience
is what allows you to sell to people
when people can feel the energy of what
it's like to work with you as a client
when they can feel what it's like
to have purchased what you're selling
when they experience inside of their
being what it's like
you've done a good job of selling now
how do you do that well you have to
actually understand what their end
dreams are and then you sell the dream
back to the person
okay so chat GPT is essentially a we're
generating
a possible dream of somebody who would
join a four-week online yoga program and
this is this is where it starts to get
really good is this step two of the
outcome generator
I wish there was a way to just do this
all in one prompt but it takes a little
bit of processing notice it took us
about took us about 10 minutes this used
to take us an hour and a half to do
about a year ago and now it takes us 10
minutes which is really cool and so this
is the process that we use for all of
our sales letters for all of our sales
copy for all of our our ads is going
through and entering these types of
questions in so this is what I love she
found this is just the the the faux fake
generated fictional story of somebody
who went through this training she had
the confidence to join a marathon
motivated to continue setting new
fitness goals
um you know led to job increase more
family time she was more present more
attentive stronger emotional connections
she created a better support network so
you see what I'm saying and and
ultimately if we think about that that
that is a very
great representation of what somebody
can experience
when they join something like a fitness
coaching or something like that is it's
ultimately that life experience you're
never going to successfully sell anybody
on what you do as a coach
on what you do as a trainer
because there's way too many people out
there quote unquote doing the same thing
so you have to be able to sell people on
the dream and the outcome that they have
and you give them that dream back to
them and you promise that dream now is a
hundred percent of every person who's
going to go through that's going to get
that dream outcome no it's not but
that's a potential dream for the type
person that's going to connect with you
and here's what I would invite you to do
this goes next level
What similarities does your story as a
coach have with this outcome right here
and what you want to do is you want to
marry those two together
your story
and your potentials client story marry
the two together
so that you can then bring people in and
create the dream ultimate outcome that
they have I'm starting to see this even
happen in our coaching business is you
know a lot of people
very smart very intelligent coaches but
they over analyze our over analytical of
the whole process guess who dealt with
that themselves myself
way too over analytical I have had to
remove that part of my brain that was
a good part of what made me powerful not
so successful when it comes to this
business of coaching and mentoring
because I would ruminate and ruminate
and ruminate and spend hours and days
and months coming up with all the best
ways to do things but I would never take
action
and so what we're finding is is that I'm
encouraging people as they start to see
how we take action how we put stuff out
there it's encouraging others to do the
same as well
okay so what I do is then I filter this
back through
and what I like is I use this expert
sales letter copywriter prompt right
here
and this is kind of a big prompt
but what it does is it filters it in a
way that it knows how to write great
sales letters
do nothing with the above
info
until I give further instructions do you
understand
I'm actually going to add that to the
bottom of this because that's really an
important part of this prompt
and it's for it to do nothing with the
above info
okay so now what we do is we're going to
tell it write a sales letter
for a free four week or it doesn't even
have to be free for a 47 dollar
four week
Yoga and Fitness
training class
whoops my cat is walking in my keyboard
based on the above in a conversational
informal tone specifically follow this
format
are you tired of issue problem I know
what it's like I've been there too
empathy story
and then give an invite to the
class
and then I have it write it twice I have
it rewrite it in the tone of Sandy
Krakowski
which by the way if you don't know why
we do that is because
it is actually trained on all the
content that we did with my mom with
Sandy Krakowski and a lot of those sales
letters I even wrote myself and so the
way that I would write a sales letter it
produces it very close to when we use
the tone of Sandy Bukowski
are you tired of feeling stressed and
out of shape I've been there too I can
help
struggling to stay motivated to stay fit
trust me I know what it's like just
years ago I was in the same boat
juggling work and family and personal
commitments left me feeling overwhelmed
and unable to prioritize my health and
well-being and if something had to
change I needed a solution that was
flexible and effective then I stumbled
upon Yoga and Fitness training and
completely transformed my life I want to
share with you this experience
introducing four-week program to regain
control of your life and your energy
levels
okay so what this is doing is this is
this is writing sales copy right here
that we could use for a sales letter you
might be saying again you haven't showed
me yet how to do Facebook ads well I'm
going to show you to make your Facebook
ad you have to have the sales copy for
your landing page written first
okay because they have to be directly
connected to each other they have to
match each other
okay
tired and out of shape I've been there
too feeling overwhelmed stressed out
like there's no time for Fitness oh
honey I feel you I've been right where
you are and it's no picnic but you know
what I found out a way and now I'm on a
mission to help you do the same
Yes you heard that right it's a rocking
program you'll get customized training
weekly sessions all right so that's a
good Baseline as far as for an offer or
some kind of a coaching program or a
four-week program that you that you're
doing with that type of language now
what we're gonna do is we're gonna say
convert the above to Pas copy
are you struggling with overwhelming
stress finding it hard to stay in shape
you're not alone I was like you caught
up in a never-ending cycle of exhaustion
the constant stress and neglect was
taking a toll on my mental health
leading to burnout decreased quality of
life and
we all deserve healthy energized life
that's where the four week program came
in it was a game changing program Define
inner peace all for this 47 bucks
perfect
all right
so then what I'm going to do is I'm
going to say convert
the above to a Facebook ad
transform your life in just four weeks
struggling with stress and finding how
hard to stay in shape you're not alone
discover the four-week yoga
transformation program that'll conquer
your stress and improve your Fitness for
just 47 you'll get a customized plan
weekly live sessions to guide you
through and access to a supportive
Community mindfulness and stress
management techniques don't let stress
and poor health
control your life any longer click the
link below to take steps forward towards
a happier healthier more Balanced Life
okay so we would we could you could
actually use this as the Facebook ad
copy the language for your Facebook ad
and that's the process that we use to
write all of our Facebook ads is we
filter it through there we work on what
our sales letter is what our offer and
then we filter it down into having chat
GPT write our sales copy we also have
this one right here
uh video ad script for Facebook and
Instagram
and we have it actually generate a video
ad are you struggling with stress
finding it hard to stay fit my name is
so and so I've been doing yoga and
fitness for 10 years I've helped
thousands of people like you transform
their lives I put together a four-week
program that's going to help beginners
just like you with this you can conquer
stress improve your Fitness find inner
peace don't wait any longer click the
link register now
and in fact let me edit this real quick
video ad script
a conversational informal and persuasive
tone
that's going to make it slightly better
let's try that if we do it in a
conversational informal and persuasive
tone
are you feeling overwhelmed with stress
and struggling to stay in shape what if
there's a solution that you could do
that would change your life
I've been helping people just like you
for years experience health and
rebalance and regain control of their
lives helped hundreds of clients
experience this even when they thought
it was impossible and I'm excited to
introduce you to this program so I
actually like the other version a little
bit better so you can try it out by
removing the conversational informal
tone tag or not
um
and see which one does better
for you
so this is how we come up with our ad
creative for our scripts for all of that
for what we're doing now what's
converting best
for Facebook ads is we're not sending
people straight to a paid offer
it it costs significantly Less in
Facebook ads to get somebody to sign up
for something that's free to get them on
your email list and then you can make
offers that cost money to them once
they're on your email list and retarget
those people and so what we do is we
recommend getting people to join you for
uh free virtual events
whether they be a free webinar
a free uh one day training kind of like
I'm doing on Zoom right here like I did
this yesterday on Saturday I'm recording
this on Sunday right
or
um this free Friday intensive May 8th
through the 12th 2023 right here okay
and so
it costs a lot less to get somebody to
join something like this than to send
them straight to a paid offer now could
you do a pre-recorded masterclass sure
however the results of pre-recorded
versus live are usually about
15 to 20 percent
of what live is you'll you'll actually
see an 80 to 90 percent drop in your
sales
um just by doing it pre-recorded overall
um could you do a free ebook sure you
could I noticed everybody who does a
pre-recorded or does an ebook they're
still eventually moving somebody to some
kind of a live experience and that's
where you can really make a connection
with your prospects the right qualified
people with you and that's where we're
closing the most amount of sales and
we're seeing the most amount of sales
come in in our businesses so
you're going to want to make sure that
you have an offer that connects with
people and that's why what we're helping
people the most with is launching and
scaling their coaching offers creating
an offer that directly speaks to what
somebody wants
connects with buyers and converts them
to sales and so if you're wanting to
start grow launch and scale your six
figure group coaching that's what we
help people with that's what we're going
to help you with that's what we help you
with on these trainings that's what this
podcast is dedicated towards and so if
you're running Facebook ads that's our
process that we use to actually come up
with and write our ad copy using chat
GPT and you can basically duplicate
exactly what I just did on your own
um and you'll see an increase in the
results in your in your ads specifically
something that I love to do a little bit
and I call it just kind of playing
around with the algorithm a little bit
is there's a third layer to this that
I'll do and this is just more of an
advanced thing
is I'll go through and I call it tossing
the ball around with chat GPT Terrell go
through and I'll run the same prompts a
couple of times so now that we've done
that I'll go through and I'll run this
again on the pain points and what I'll
start to do is I'll start to I'll copy
them to a separate document and then
I'll start to tag which ones really
really speak to what I know is
specifically what I solve as the
solution to somebody what I can help
people with and then I I copy that to a
separate uh text document or a Google
doc
on my computer and then I'll bring that
back into chat GPT and have it process
what I call the the um the best of the
best so what it is is chat gbt is
generating all this text here on this
page now we have a lot of text going on
this page there's a lot of different
pieces of text
but what you'll notice is from the
output of the text I have people and the
exercise might take about 10 minutes I'm
not going to do it right here but what I
recommend you do is you go through what
it's generated and you copy and paste
whatever really stands out to you that's
relevant to your clients to the problems
you solve and the promotion that you're
wanting to do copy that into a text
document and then reprocess that through
the same
process that we just went through and it
will like 5 to 10x improve your results
because you're just taking the best of
the best and feeding that into it and
that's really going to help you dial in
your sales copy even more and so what I
tell people to do is iterate with chat
GPT don't just take the one single
output that it has start to edit it
start to tune it start to tweak it a
little bit and it will pay you dividends
okay
listen if you want to learn more about
growing a coaching business getting more
clients that's what we help people with
stay plugged into this podcast listen
through the different episodes of this
podcast stay plugged into my YouTube
channel my my social media profiles and
make sure to join us on one of the live
events that we're doing that's where we
bring the best most Cutting Edge content
to you and if you want support guidance
accountability and a community of people
that are growing and building their
businesses together to get results
faster
join the client growth accelerator when
the doors open to it make sure that you
get on the waiting list we can't wait to
have you in there all right everybody
grow your life we'll talk soon